Beaches everywhere have been
thronged with beachgoers for days on end.
各地の海水浴場は連日大にぎわいを見せています
Look at this!
The shore is packed with beach umbrellas.
- Yumigahama Beach in Kohoku
looks just like a flower garden.
- Swimsuit?
"New Mail: 1"
"0001 No Subject - Mikazuki Yozora"
"0002 No Subject - Kashiwazaki Sena"
"0003 No Subject - Mikazuki Yozora"
"Mikazuki Yozora"
"Be at the club at 2:00.
Everyone bring a swimsuit."
- Yumigahama Beach in Kohoku
looks just like a flower garden.
- Swimsuit?
"Be at the club at 2:00.
Everyone bring a swimsuit."
水着
Kobato, what's wrong?
小鳩 どうした
Kobato-chan!
小鳩ちゃ～ん
Hi, Kobato-chan!
小鳩ちゃん こんにちは
No.
いや
What should we play today?
今日は何して遊びましょうか
No!
いや
Kobato-chan, did you bring your swimsuit too?!
小鳩ちゃんも水着持ってきたの
No!
いや
アハハッ 超拒否られてる
She's totally rejecting me!
Did you bring a swimsuit, Sena?
星奈も水着持ってきたのか
ええ 夜空のバカに言われて一応ね
Yeah. Stupid Yozora said to, so just in case.
小鳩ちゃんったら
- We're here.
- Oh, Kobato-chan!
うぃ～っす
Horse?!
馬
QUIVER
Vigorously bursting with goodness
You know, that's surprisingly addicting
Let's get the ball rolling
while you're idly acting shy!
Let's make friends and play, yeah!
"Haganai"
I look cool, but I'm actually super lonely
(My delusions went bye, bye, bye
Best friends are a nope, nope, nope, nope)
I'm not held back any, but this isn't enough
(Is a happy life in the real world far, far, far away?
Best friends are a nope, nope, nope, nope)
If a group of unlucky people gathered together,
Ah... I can't picture it
This situation is like stepping on a mine!
FIDGET
I totally, totally want to take a peek
I don't want to regret this 100 times
Totally toss aside and
shake off that boring pride
Unfortunately, this idea popped into my mind,
and you know, it's surprisingly addicting
Let's find some as we
clash and rattle each other!
Let's make friends and play, yeah!
本字幕由诸神卖萌组(kamigami.org)出品  仅供交流学习之用 禁止用于商业用途
---诸神卖萌组---
日听:安少   翻译:银苹果   校对:喵儿&小草爱吃梨   时间轴&后期:亢奋的蛇
I totally, totally want to take a peek
You! Toss aside and shake yourself off
Yes! Well? What do you think of that?
"The President's Recollections are Painful"
I never would've guessed that I'd encounter
まさかこのような場所で魔人アシュタロスと遭遇しようとは
the demon Astaroth in a place like this...
But I thought the Evil Gate was destroyed
during the last war between God and the Devil!
しかしイヴィルゲートは先の神魔大戦で崩壊したはず
そういうのはいいから
Never mind about that...
Yozora?
夜空
えっ 夜空か
That's Yozora?!
Indeed.
いかにも
What the heck are you doing?
Are you an idiot? A fool?
何やってんの あんた
バカなの アホなの
W-What?
な...何よ
Don't come near me! That's gross!
近づかないでよ キモい
Ow!
痛っ
Hey! What was that for?
何すんのよ
- What the hell does she want?
- Hey! That hurt!
一体何がしたいんだ
Today is Swimsuit Day.
今日は水着デーなのです
Swimsuit Day?
水着デー
The plan is to wear swimsuits at the club.
水着で部活をしようという企画です
Why would we do that?
何でそんなことを
Because it would be a shame not
to wear my swimsuit after I bought it.
せっかく水着を買ったのに着ないのはもったいないからだ
It's your fault, you and Rika, for going home!
あんた達が帰っちゃうのが悪いんでしょうが
Well, we left soon after that, too.
まあ 俺達もすぐに帰ったんだけどな
The pool was so crowded,
it was impossible to have fun.
プールめちゃくちゃ混んでた遊べなかった
Is that true?!
それは本当か
Y-Yeah...
What happened?
どうした
I mean, what's with the horse mask?
つか その馬マスクは何なんだ
And on top of that, you're wearing
a full-body zebra-like swimsuit...
おまけに縞馬みたいな全身水着だし
It's embarrassing to display your flesh
where there are a lot of people, isn't it?
人が大勢いるところで肌を露出させるなど 恥ずかしいではないか
With this, my flesh isn't exposed,
and no one can see my face,
これなら肌を晒すこともなく顔も見られないから
so I'm not embarrassed.
恥ずかしくない
If you'd gone to the pool wearing
that, people would've been pissed.
その格好でプールに入ったら間違いなく怒られてたぞ
There's no rule against
swimming with a mask on, is there?
マスクをかぶって泳いではいけないという決まりはないだろ
But there is a rule against
weird stuff in the pool.
変なものをプールに入れるなって決まりならあるわよ
Then you wouldn't get in, huh?
じゃあ お前は入れないな
What was that?!
何ですって
When you go in the pool, the whole pool...
肉がプールなんかに入ったら
Kodaka-sempai!
小鷹先輩
Rika is wearing a swimsuit under her lab coat.
白衣の下の理科は水着です
Want to see?!
見たいですか
No, not especially.
いや 特には
Listen to me!
- If you look, I'm sure you'll be surprised.
- Stupid Yozora!
見たらきっと驚きますよ
Rika calls it..."The Emperor's
New Clothes" swimsuit!
名付けて バカには見えない水着
That's just going nude!
それはただの全裸だろう
So take a look!
それでは ご覧ください
Knock it off, idiot!
や...やめろ バカ
Just kidding.
な～んて嘘ですよ
Well? How does Rika look in her swimsuit?
どうです 理科の水着姿
Kind of normal...
何か普通だな
N-Normal?!
ふ...普通
Normal is only the outward appearance!
普通なのは外見だけ
- Actually, this swimsuit
becomes translucent in hot water!
- Cut it out!
実は この水着お湯につけると透明になる特殊繊維でできてます
"Mixed Bathing Hot Spring"
小鷹先輩と 混浴の温泉に行って
Rika will go with Kodaka-sempai
to a mixed bathing hot spring,
and Sempai will think it's a
swimsuit, but before his eyes,
水着だなと油断している先輩の目の前で
Rika will emerge from
the hot water, totally naked!
お湯につかった理科が全裸に
Sempai will lose control and follow his
carnal desires that surge up from within!
理性を失った先輩が ほとばしる獣欲のおもむくままに
Not gonna happen.
I'd never go to a hot spring with you.
お前と一緒に温泉に行くことなんて絶対ない
Seriously?
マジですか
"Maria"
あ お兄ちゃん
Big Brother!
いたっ いたっ
Ow...
ああ か...怪獣 怪獣がおる
M-Monster! There's a monster in here!
It's okay. She's...
大丈夫だ こいつは
I'm gonna munch on you!
オレサマ オマエ マルカジリ
You can't eat me! I'm raw! I'm no good raw!
食べられないです
なまもの なまものだから
I'll grill you good first, and then eat you.
チャントヨク焼イテ食ベル
I-I-I still won't taste good, even grilled!
や...焼いてもおいしくありません
Because I've been eating vegetables lately!
最近野菜も食べてるから
I'm a vegetarian!
オレサマ ベジタリアン
うわっ こんなことならステーキ食べるのやめるんじゃなかった
If I knew this was gonna happen,
I wouldn't have stopped eating steak!
- I should've given myself a fat, flabby taste!
- She isn't eating steak?
ぶくぶくのお肉味になればよかった
ステーキ食ってないのか
- Recently, Maria-dono has
said that normal food is fine, so...
- I'm gonna be eaten!
最近はマリア殿から
- Recently, Maria-dono has
said that normal food is fine, so...
- Wait! Wait! Don't move around!
普通でいいと言われておりますので
ククク ゆくのだ魔人アシュタロトよ
Go, Astarot!
その生意気な神の手先を頭からボリボリ食べてしまえ
Start at the head and munch your
way down that uppity agent of God!
I thought it was "Astaroth"...
アシュタロスじゃなかったっけ
S-So you're a friend of the vampire?!
やっぱり吸血鬼の仲間か
Stupid dummy idiot poopy vampire!
バカバカ アホ ウンコ吸血鬼
Die!
お前なんか死んでまえ
ククク 死ぬのは貴様だ
You're the one who's gonna die!
オレサマ オマエボリボリ食ベル ボリボリ食ベル ボリボリ...
I'm gonna munch on you!
- Help me, Big Brother!
- Munch-munch-munch-munch!
助けて お兄ちゃん
That's enough, Yozora.
その辺にしておけ 夜空
Fine.
そうする
The horse turned into Yozora!
馬が夜空になった
Why?! Why-Why-Why?!
何で 何で何で何で
This is a cursed mask.
これは呪いのマスクだ
If you put it on, the demon Astro possesses you.
かぶると魔人明日太郎に意識を乗っ取られてしまう
Whoops. The power of
darkness is moving my hands...
おっと 手が闇の力に
I can't see anything! It's pitch-black!
真っ暗で何も見えないぞ
It's proof that the power of
darkness has invaded your mind!
それは貴様の精神が闇の力に侵食されている証拠だ
I don't wanna be a horse monster! Help me!
馬怪獣になんかなりたくない 助けて
ククク 助かりたくば二度とあんちゃんに近づかぬと誓え
If you want help, swear you'll
never go near my Bro again!
I refuse! I love Big Brother!
いやだ お兄ちゃん好き
Don't you dare say, "I love Big Brother!"
お兄ちゃん好きなんか言うな
Yay! The curse was broken!
やった 呪いが解けたぞ
That's what you get, little turd!
ざまあみろクソが
Why, you... um... uh...
この えっと えとえと
Idiot!
アホ
アホっていう方がアホだ このうんこ吸血鬼め
- Look, Yozora, if you don't want your swimsuit
to go to waste, how about visiting the beach?
- Takes one to know one! Poopy vampire!
ていうか夜空さ
水着無駄にしたくないなら海に行くのはどう
- Look, Yozora, if you don't want your swimsuit
to go to waste, how about visiting the beach?
- Shut up, poopy church girl!
うっさいわこのうんこ聖職者
- The beach is packed with people.
- If I'm "poopy," you're a super-stupid poopy!
海なんて人がいっぱいだろうが
うんこっていうお前がアホうんこ決定だ
- What about my family's private beach?
- If I'm "poopy," you're a super-stupid poopy!
あたしんちのプライベートビーチにでも行く
ならあんたはうちのこと吸血鬼って言ったら吸血鬼だ
- What about my family's private beach?
- Then if you call me a vampire, you're a vampire!
- Y-You have one?!
ほ...本当か それ
Yeah. We've got a summer
house, which has a beach...
ええ 別荘があってそこに
That's what makes her one of the bourgeois!
これだからブルジョアは
Well, to be honest, I've only
been there once, when I was little.
まあ 実はあたしも小さい頃に１回行っただけなんだけどね
It's so far that you have to
stay overnight, which is a pain...
遠くて泊りがけで行くことになるから なかなか
So... we could hold a training camp
at your summer house, Sena-sempai?
つまり 星奈先輩んちの別荘で
合宿ができるということですか
I see... Training camp...
そっか 合宿か
They often have them in gal games, you know?
ギャルゲーでも よくあるわよね
To be sure, that is a traditional club activity.
確かに部活っぽいな
Well, it could be a good
experience to prepare us
まあ リア充になった時に備えて
そういうのを経験しておくのもいいかもしれないな
for when we become "happy people"...
Then I'll ask Daddy.
それじゃあ パパに頼んどくわ
So... it's okay to set it up?
て 決めちゃっていいの
Does anyone have other plans?
みんな他に予定とかは
We're all free anytime,
since none of us have any friends.
いつでもＯＫだ
なぜならみんな友達いないからな
Not a pleasing thing to hear...
喜べない話だ
Hey, hey, what's a training camp?
なな 合宿って何なのだ
Hmm... I suppose a training
camp needs its adviser, too...
ふん 合宿には顧問も必要か
If you look up, you'll see the wide blue sky
and, set against it, towering Mt. Asano.
At its base is a stream
of refreshing spring water.
Yes?
はい
H-Herlo...
も もしも...
Hello! I'm Kashiwazaki Sena...
もしもし わたくし 柏崎星奈ですけど
I-Is Kodaka-kun there?
こ...小鷹君いますか
Relax, Sena! This is my cell phone.
落ち着け星奈 これは俺の携帯だ
Oh... oh yeah, that's right.
えっ そう...それもそうね
So... do you want something?
それで 何か用か
A-Are you free today? Kobato-chan, too...
あんた 今日暇
小鳩ちゃんも
Just the club after lunch...
この後は部活くらいだが
Then come to my house today.
じゃあ 今日うちに来て
Remember what you said before?
About wanting to pay respects to my father...
ほら 前に言ってたでしょ
パパに挨拶したいって
Oh. But this is all of a sudden...
あ～ って随分急だな
Yeah. When I asked him about the
summer house today, I mentioned your name,
うん 今日別荘の話をした時 あんたの名前出したらさ
and Daddy said he wanted to see you in a hurry.
何かパパが急いで会いたいって言い出したのよ
Why?
何で
I don't know. But, anyway, okay?
さあ とにかくＯＫ
Well... gotcha.
まあ 了解
Then I'll tell you how to get here and the time.
じゃあ 来方と時間言うから
な...メモ取るから
I'll write it down...
"The Collected Works of Akutagawa Ryunosuke"
[Known as the "Father of the Japanese Short Story"]
This is the due date.
返却日はこちらです
"Taka - No Subject"
"Meat - No Subject"
"Taka"
"Kobato and I won't be at the club today."
"Won't be there," he says?
休むだと
"Meat"
"I'm taking the day off."
"The Collected Works of Akutagawa Ryunosuke"
"Ultra-Mecha"
There?
あれか
"Private Property"
It's easy to tell...
分かりやすっ
U-Um...
あ...あの
Welcome.
いらっしゃいませ
You're Hayato's children, aren't you?
隼人の子供達だな
I'm Sena's father.
私は星奈の父だ
I'm the president of the academy.
学園の理事長をしている
は...はじめまして理事長 羽瀬川小鷹です
It's a pleasure to meet you,
President! I'm Hasegawa Kodaka.
This is my younger sister, Kobato.
こっちは妹の小鳩
You resemble Hayato, with a brazen-looking face.
隼人に似てふてぶてしそうな顔をしている
And this one has Airi-san's face.
こっちはアイリさんの面影があるな
A meal has been prepared. Come.
食事の準備がしてある 来なさい
Wait. Sir, you haven't
given your own name yet...
お待ちを
まだ旦那様がお名前を名乗っていらっしゃいません
グッ わ...私は
I'm Kashiwazaki...
柏崎
My name is...
名前は
...written with the characters "ten" and "uma."
["heaven" and "horse"]
天の馬と書く
Kashiwazaki... Tenma-san?
柏崎... てんまさんですか
It reads as "Pegasus."
ペガサスと読むのです
Pegasus?
ペガサス
You don't call me by that name!
その名前で俺を呼ぶんじゃない
I mean... It isn't that
dignified a name, you know?
いや あまり...その
威厳のある名前ではないだろう
For that reason...
で あるからして
I-I understand...
分かりました
I'm Stella, the house steward.
わたくしは家令のステラと申します
Steward?
カレー
Please don't stare at me like that, Kodaka-sama.
まじまじと見つめないでください 小鷹様
I'll get pregnant.
子供ができてしまいます
Is a steward the same thing as a butler?
家令って執事ですか
At first, I thought Stella-san
was maybe Sena... - san's mother...
俺 最初ステラさんは星奈...さんの お母さんかと
My wife is currently abroad.
妻は現在外国にいるんだ
But it's rare for you to
meet guests at the door, Daddy.
ていうか パパが玄関にお客さんを迎えに行くのって
珍しいわね
I was passing by.
ついでだ
He's been fidgeting to
meet the two of you for a while.
お二人に早くお会いしたくて
ずっとソワソワしておられたのです
I-I have not!
べ...別にそういうわけではない
Now just bring the food out!
さっさと料理を出せ
As you wish.
承知しました
Please go ahead, everyone.
皆様どうぞ
Thank you for the food!
いただきま～す
Eat a lot, okay, Kobato-chan?
小鳩ちゃん いっぱい食べてね
With good manners, Kobato.
行儀よくな 小鳩
Thank you for the food.
いただきます
Well, thank you for the food.
それじゃあ いただきます
U-Um, thank you for helping
us transfer into the academy.
あの 編入の際は ありがとうございました
It seems like my dad asked for a big favor...
何か親父が無理を言ったみたいで
He did indeed.
まったく そのとおりだ
Right when the entrance
season was over, suddenly
入学シーズンが終わったところに いきなり
that idiot demanded, " Enroll my son
and daughter in that school of yours."
ちょっとそっちの学校で息子と娘の面倒を見てやってくれ
などと あのバカは
I-I apologize for that...
な...何かすみません
Even though you're his son,
you're very well-mannered.
やつの息子のくせに 礼儀をわきまえているようだな
Oh, that's right! Here. This isn't much, but...
そうだ これ
ささやかなものですが
"Kuriya"
What is this?
何これ
The "It's salty and spicy, but is also like
deeply-flavored life: Rayu" assortment.
[Rayu: famous Japanese brand of spicy sesame oil]
「しょっぱくもあり辛くもあり
しかし味わい深い人生にも似たラー油」詰め合わせ
What's that mean?
何それ
Well, it really is delicious!
それ本当に おいしいんだって
It goes with rice, pasta, anything.
ご飯でもパスタでも何にでも合うし
Even Kobato likes it, and she hates spicy stuff.
辛いの苦手な小鳩もこれは好きだし
Can I open one?
開けてもいいかね
Please, go ahead.
どうぞ どうぞ
うん うまい
Good!
Yeah, you're right! This is delicious!
本当 おいしいじゃない
Glad you like it.
よかった
Bro, me too!
あんちゃん うちも
や～ん お姉ちゃんが食べさせてあげる
Your big sister will feed you!
そういえば隼人も
- Come to think of it, Hayato
has always been good at finding
- Okay, open wide!
こういう変わった食べ物や調味料を見つけてくるのがうまかったな
- Come to think of it, Hayato
has always been good at finding
- No!
- these kinds of unusual foods and seasonings.
- Come on, eat your big sister's!
- Well, almost as long as I can
remember, we've moved all over Japan...
- No!
まあ 昔から日本全国を転々としてますし
- Well, almost as long as I can
remember, we've moved all over Japan...
- So cute! Say, "Aaaaah!"
This time, he suddenly went abroad...
今回もいきなり海外に行っちゃって
Even after all these years,
that man hasn't changed.
本当に昔から変わらんな あの男は
It must have been hard on you two.
君達も大変だったな まったく
- Unbelievable, devoting himself to digging up
ruins, even dragging you kids into it, the scum!
- It's yummy!
- Unbelievable, devoting himself to digging up
ruins, even dragging you kids into it, the scum!
- No!
子供まで巻き込んで遺跡掘りなんぞにうつつを抜かしおって
- Unbelievable, devoting himself to digging up
ruins, even dragging you kids into it, the scum!
- Big sister's gobbling up Kobato-chan!
あのクズめ
He's not scum!
クズなんかじゃ
S-Sorry...
す...すいません
Um, our father isn't scum.
あの うちの父はクズではないです
Though he may be stupid...
バカかもしれないけど
I know that.
そんなことは知っている
えっ 泊まり...ですか
Stay over?
There's no need to hesitate.
遠慮することはない
No, it's not hesitation...
いや 遠慮とかじゃなくて
Actually, on Saturday and Sunday, there
are no buses to Tooya Station after 8pm.
実は土日は８時以降
遠夜駅方面のバスはありません
If you absolutely must
get home, I could drive you...
どうしてもと おっしゃるのなら
わたくしが車をお出ししますが
...but to be honest, it would be a pain.
正直 面倒くさいです
It'd be a pain?
いや 面倒くさいって
Just stay over!
泊まっていけばいいじゃない
いや パジャマとかも持って来てないし
But we didn't bring pajamas or anything...
You can use my nightclothes.
私の寝間着を使うといい
That's what Hayato always
did when he stayed over.
隼人が泊まる時はいつもそうしていた
I think my old pajamas
would fit you, Kobato-chan.
小鳩ちゃんは あたしが昔着てたのが合うと思うわ
But the room, or...
いや 部屋とか
We have a guest room.
来客用の部屋がある
Um...
えっと
Thank you for your kind offer.
お世話になります
はあ～ 寝顔も超可愛いわ
She's super-cute when she's sleeping, too!
Don't touch her!
手出すんじゃねえぞ
Anyway, it seems Daddy really likes you.
にしても あんた パパに随分気に入られたみたいね
I haven't seen him in that
good a mood for a long time.
あんなに機嫌がいいパパ 久しぶりに見たわ
That was his good mood?
あれで機嫌がいいのか
A great mood!
超いいわよ
Bro, where are we?
あんちゃん
ここ どこ
Say, Kobato-chan, why don't we take
a bath together before going to bed?
ねえねえ小鳩ちゃん
寝る前に一緒にお風呂入ろっか
Take a bath...
お風呂 入る
You know, Kobato, it wouldn't
hurt you to skip one night...
いや 小鳩
無理に入らなくても...
それじゃ行きましょう お風呂
Then let's go to the bath!
President...
理事長
Have a drink with me.
付き合いたまえ
Um, I'm a minor...
あの 俺未成年なんですが
This is regular grape juice. Relax.
こっちは ただの葡萄ジュースだ
安心したまえ
I don't know about this...
紛らわしい
This is the real thing.
こっちが本物 取り替えようか
Shall we trade?
No, like I said, I'm...
いや ですから
Just kidding.
冗談だ
In our student days, Hayato
and I often drank like this.
学生時代は よくこうして隼人と飲んだものだ
So I'm standing in for Dad...
俺は父さんの代わりってわけか
You can really down it!
いい飲みっぷりだ
It's not alcohol!
お酒じゃないですって
Um... are you okay?
あの 大丈夫ですか
Huuuh? S'what okay?
あッ にゃにがじゃ
That was quick!
出来上がり早っ
In our shtudent daysh,
Hayato and I often drank like thish!
がきゅせいじだいは ひょくきょうしてはやととのんだ
In our shtudent daysh...
がきゅせいじだいは...
In our... In our shtudent daysh...
がきゅせい...じだい
President!
理事長
President, please wake up!
理事長起きてください
P-President?
り...理事長
Should I call Stella-san?
ステラさん呼ぶか
Kobato!
小鳩
Bro!!
あんちゃ～ん
- What's wrong?!
- Wait, Kobato-chan!
どうしたんだ
待って 小鳩ちゃ～ん
Ow...
イタタッ...
Wh-Wh-Wh-What are you doing here, Kodaka?!
ななな...何でこんな所に小鷹がいるのよ
Stupid idiot dirty molester poopy pervert
brute main character of an erotic game!
バカ アホ エッチ 痴漢 うんこ 変態 鬼畜 エロゲー主人公
Th-That's 100% my line!
そりゃ１００パーセントこっちのセリフだ
Universe!!
ユニバ～ス
She ran outside...
行ってしまった
I don't believe it. Seriously?
ウソだろ おい
Oh, dear. Dirty-minded Kodaka-san.
いや～ 小鷹さんのエッチ～
No! Um, that was just an accident...
いやあの 今のは事故なんで
I know.
分かっております
Come, Kobato-sama, while you have a chance...
さあ 小鳩様 今のうちに
Okay.
U-Um, the President is sleeping on the bed...
あの 理事長がベッドで寝ちゃってるんですけど
Once the Master falls asleep, he
absolutely won't awaken 'til morning.
旦那様は一度眠ってしまわれると
絶対に朝まで起きません
I'll have Kobato-sama
sleep in the servants' room.
小鳩様ははたくしども使用人の部屋でお預かりいたしますので
So, my apologies, but
please sleep in the same bed
申し訳ありませんが 小鷹様は
旦那様と同じベッドでお休みくださいませ
with the Master tonight, Kodaka-sama.
I-I'll sleep in the servants' room, too...
お...俺もそっちの部屋で
I sleep in the nude.
わたくしは寝る時全裸です
I'll sleep with the President.
理事長と一緒に寝ます
No!
You often drank together in your student days...
学生時代はよく一緒に飲んだ か
No question, the President
thinks of my dad as a close friend.
理事長は間違いなく俺の父さんを親友だと思ってくれている
I'm sure that's why Dad could leave
だから父さんは俺と小鳩を日本に残して
Kobato and me in Japan and go off on a journey.
旅立つ決断ができたんだろう
I wonder if I'll ever make
a friend like that someday...
俺にもいつか
そんな友達ができるんだろうか
Well, thank you for everything.
それじゃあ
どうも色々とお世話になりました
Kobato?
小鳩
Th-Thank you for everything.
お世話になりました
You're welcome to come back anytime.
またいつでも来るといい
Thank you.
ありがとうございます
Next time, let's take
another bath together, okay?
今度また 一緒にお風呂入ろうね
No!
いや
いや～
- Nooooooooooo!!
- Kobato!
小鳩
What'd you do to her?
お前 何したんだ
I didn't do anything!
別に何もしてないわよ
That aside, Kodaka...
それより 小鷹
うん 何だ
What?
U-Um, about what happened last night...
あの 昨日の夜のことなんだけどさ
えっ 昨日の夜
Last night?
Sorry, the President made
me drink wine last night,
すまん 昨日は理事長にワイン飲まされてさ
and I was so drunk that
I don't remember anything.
酔っ払って何も覚えてないんだ
- Did something happen?
- Um... well... that is...
何かあったのか
いや その
何でもない
Nothing!
Kobato-chan! Wait!
小鳩ちゃん 待って～
The best thing to do is not
remember anything, even if it is a lie.
嘘でも何も覚えてないことにしておくのが一番だ
Kodaka-kun...
小鷹君
Yes?
はい
Wh-What?!
な...何でしょう
Please take good care of my daughter!
娘を よろしく頼む
O-Of course...
もちろんです
...Pegasus-san!
ペガサスさん
Y-You wretch!
き...貴様
Well, excuse me.
それじゃあ 失礼します
Knock that off! Stella!
こ～ら ステラ
"0001 No Subject - Kashiwazaki Sena"
"0002 No Subject - Mikazuki Yozora"
"Kashiwazaki Sena"
"You really don't remember anything
about last night, right? Really?"
"Kodaka"
"Really, really, really."
"0001 No Subject - Mikazuki Yozora"
"0002 No Subject - Kashiwazaki Sena"
"Mikazuki Yozora"
"Monday, Club at 2:00."
"Incoming Mail..."
"Taka - No Subject"
"Meat - No Subject"
"Taka"
"Roger!"
All right!
よし
Ah, my mind is escaping
reality as ideally as imaginable
Not that it really matters
now if I... make friends
Those eyes that belittle me saying,
"You're a lonesome person on your own," bug me
So, while I was thinking that it'd be cool...
...if only a superficial group gathered up,
They show up, one here,
one there, and gather together
The unique characters
Throw me off balance
It ticks me off! Especially that mean meat!
My chest is secretly filled with
apprehension and I feel a bit indecisive
I can't tell you what's in my heart
Am I the one disappointed by that?
Plow through the fog today!
Ever since the day I got left behind,
my maiden heart has been filled with regret
Hurry and find it...my lost heart
When I woke up in the morning, an old man's
sleeping face was only centimeters away from me!
朝目覚めると
目の前数センチの所におっさんの寝顔があった
Hayato...
隼人～
最悪だ
Oh, God... You say my dad's name in your sleep?!
っていうか寝言で親父の名前かよ
私は一体
W-Where?! W-What did you do to me?!
君は何をした
What are you doing in my bed?!
なぜ私のベッドにお前がいる
I'm Hasegawa Kodaka and...
いや俺は羽瀬川小鷹で
I mean, this is my bed!
っていうかここは俺のベッドで
You're the one who suddenly
fell asleep here in the first...
いきなり寝たのは そもそも
You didn't do anything?!
何もしてない
どこの美少女だよ あんた
What are you, a beautiful girl?
Next time: "No One Sleeps at Camp."
"Next time: No One Sleeps at Camp"
次回「合宿はみんなが寝ない」
Really? I'll never forgive you if you're lying!
本当に 嘘だったら
ぜ...絶対に許さないんだからね
も...萌えるじゃねえか
Th-That's actually pretty cute...